otteny.com 2017-02-24

# OTTE | Privacy Policy

OTTE is committed to protecting the privacy interests of our customers. We are highly sensitive in maintaining the trust of our customers and we provide this policy so that you are able to understand what personally identifiable or personal information we may collect from you when you visit our website, how we use such information, and the choices you have with respect to our use of this information. 

In this Privacy Policy, the terms "we", "our", and "us" refer to OTTE and OTTENY.COM. 

##### Personally Identifiable Information

In this Privacy Policy, the terms "personal information" or "personally identifiable information" refers to any information by which you can be identified or contacted, such as your name, mailing address, telephone number, e-mail address, etc. 

##### What type of information does Otte Collect?

We collect personal information, as defined above, when you visit our website, place an order online or by phone, make an in-store purchase, save your information with us online, contact us with a question or participate in any promotional activities we conduct. We maintain records of your purchase history and product interests. We may combine all of this information with personal information about you collected from other third parties, to improve your shopping experience. 

##### How does OTTE use your personal information?

We use your personal information that we collect to help us learn more about your shopping preferences and to provide you with the best possible products and services. In providing the best possible service and products, we may share your personal information with third parties that provide support services to us or that help us market our products and services. Third-parties, who provide services on our behalf, are contractually prohibited from using your information in any manner other than helping us to provide you with products and services available from OTTE. We may share your personal information if necessary, in our good faith judgment, to comply with laws, regulations, government requests, orders, valid subpoenas or to protect the rights of OTTE or others. 

We may use your personal information to send periodic emails to provide you with information and updates regarding special offers and sales events. If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can find detailed instructions to unsubscribe at the bottom of each of our 

##### Usage of cookies with respect to your personal information

Otteny.com uses "cookie" technology that allows our site and our service providers to recognize your browser, distinguish you from other customers and further enhance and personalize your online shopping experience. Cookies are small data files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer hard drive that allows your browser to capture and remember specific information. 

For example, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can improve our website design, as well as our products, services and promotions. We contract with third-party advertising partners to assist us better in understanding our website visitors. These third-party advertising partners are not permitted to use information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. 

If you prefer, you can modify your browser settings to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to decline cookies. Declining cookies, however, may prevent you from taking full advantage of our website. 

##### Otte's use of third-party advertising partners

We use third-party advertising partners to provide advertisements on our behalf throughout the Internet. These companies may collect anonymous information (non-personally identifiable information) about your visits to Otteny.com and your interaction with our products and services. In addition to the anonymous information gathered from your visits to Otteny.com, our third-party advertising partners may also use anonymous information gathered from your visits to other websites to provide tailored advertisements for product and services available from Otteny.com. Our third-party advertisers collect information through the use of industry-standard cookie technology. 

Otteny.com currently contracts with Google for third-party advertising services. In the future we may contract with additional third-party advertising services and will provide you notice and an opportunity to opt-out from receiving cookies from these third-party advertising services. 

If you would like further information about third-party advertising technologies and choose not to have your information used by third-party advertising partners, please visit: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

##### How does OTTE protect your information?

In addition to physical, contractual and managerial security measures, Otte implements Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to safeguard the confidentiality and security of any personal information transmitted over our website. SSL technology transmits your personal information in encrypted form, and only Otte is able to decode and access your personal information. Our SSL certificate type is through VeriSign, the industry leader in authentication services that facilitate secure online commerce. You can be assured that you are on a secure connection by noting that the URL of all pages requiring the transmission or collection of personal information use the secure http protocal, https://. Please note that only information transmitted over Otteny.com is considered secured and encrypted, any information transmitted over e-mail will not be transmitted via SSL and is not considered a secured means of transmission. 

##### Third party links

We may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, in order to best serve you and protect the integrity of our site, we welcome any feedback about these sites at: [service@otteny.com](mailto:service@otteny.com)

##### Children's online policy protection act compliance

Otte is in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Otte will never knowingly collect personal information online from anyone under the age of 13 without prior verifiable parental consent. 

##### Changes to this privacy policy

This privacy policy supersedes all prior privacy disclosures provided to you from Otte. Should any material changes be made to this privacy policy, we will post the updated policy on our website and update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on 06/01/2011.
